Julie
Julie.
호놀룰루 경찰이 왔군요
The HPD escort's here.
여기 계세요
Stay here.
제가 올 때까지 기다리세요
Wait till I come for you.
정말로 감사해요, Frank
I really want
to thank you, Frank.
그리고 저를 돌봐 주시느라
가족과 얼마나 떨어져서 지내셨는지도
I know how long you've been
away from your family,
잘 알고 있어요
looking after me.
그게 제 직업이잖습니까
It's the job.
하지만 말만이라도 감사해요
But I appreciate that.
도망치는 거...
The running...
저 더 이상 못하겠어요
I can't do it anymore.
오늘 증언만 하고 나면,
더 이상 도망치는 일도 없을 겁니다
After you testify today,
the running stops.
새롭게 시작할 수 있어요, Julie
You're going to get
a fresh start, Julie.
금방 돌아올게요
I'll be right back.
연방 보안관 Frank Moore입니다
Frank Moore, U.S. Marshals.
만나서 반갑습니다
It's good to meet you.
저는 Tim Callahan 경관이고,
I'm Officer
Tim Callahan.
이쪽은 제 파트너
Joe Lee 경관입니다
This is my partner,
Officer Joe Lee.
당신과 목격자 분을
We're here
to escort you
법원까지 모시러 왔습니다
and the witness
to the courthouse.
저희는 표식 없는 차량에 타도록 하죠
She rides with me
in the unmarked.
당신들은 경찰차에 타고
앞쪽에서 운전하도록 해요
You guys
are out front.
무전기도 준비했습니까?
You got a radio for me?
그럼요 당연하죠
Yeah. Of course.
먼 거리를 이동할 때는
Man, when you guys
say remote location,
그게 필수잖습니까
you're not kidding.
그녀를 데려오죠
I'll go get her.
그 여자가 여기 있어
She's in here.
Hawaii Five-0 S01E16 E Malama
Original Air Date on February 7, 2010
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for wwwaddic7edcom ==
♪ Hawaii Five-O 1x16 ♪
E Malama
Original Air Date on February 7, 2010
DCinside 기타 미국드라마 갤러리 레바테인
번역자 정보 수정 금지, 그 외 수정배포 자유
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
음
Mmm.
친 호 켈리
Chin Ho Kelly?
왜?
Yo.
이건 말야,
단 하나의 의심의 여지도 없이
That is,
without a doubt,
내 인생에서 먹어 본 음식 중
최고의 맛이었어
the greatest thing
I've ever tasted in my life.
불량식품일지도 모르겠지만
그런 건 상관없어 진짜 맛있네
This should be illegal,
it's so good.
이게 대체 뭐야?
What the hell is it?
Coco puff라고 하지
Coco puffs.
Liliha 제과점에서 파는데,
Liliha Bakery
sells, like,
하루에 7천 개나 팔린다고
7,000 of these a day.
이걸 만든 사람은 천재야
It's genius.
- 정말 맛있네 뭘로 만든 거래?
- 버터, 크림,
It's amazing. What is it?
Butter, cream,
초콜릿, 거기에 버터 조금 더
chocolate,
a little more butter.
내가 평소에 항상 생각하는 게,
죽기 전에 마지막으로 먹는 음식이
You know, I always thought
that I wanted my last meal
우리 엄마 라자냐였으면 했는데,
to be my mother's lasagna,
이젠 더 이상 아니야
but that is out.
It's out. No more.
죽기 전에 이걸 먹고 싶어
디저트도 필요 없고,
I want this.
I want no dessert.
에피타이저도 필요 없어
이거만 한 박스 있으면 좋겠어
I want no appetizer.
Just a big box of these.
그려
Nice.
네 딸 엄마 아니야?
Wasn't that the mother
of your child?
모든 시대를 통틀어서
가장 뛰어난 발명품이 뭔지 알아?
You know what the greatest
invention of all time is?
뭔데?
What?
'전화 거절하기' 버튼이지
It's the
"ignore" button.
내 장담하는데, 핸드폰을 발명한 사람은
You know, I have a theory--
whoever invented
분명 이혼을 했었던 게 틀림없어
the modern cellular phone
also had an ex-wife.
뭐 이혼한 것 치곤 나쁘지 않은 사이 같은데?
I thought you guys
were doing better, though.
그건 맞는 말이긴 하지
하지만 다른 놈이랑 결혼했잖아
Yeah. But she's still
married to another guy.
무슨 말인지 알겠어?
You know what I mean?
한 놈한테 화풀이하는 게 속편하거든
I mean, it's a lot easier
being angry at one person.
게다가 레이첼하고 나 사이에는
우리만의 대화법이 있지
Besides, Rachel and I,
we have our own language.
말하자면 이런 거야
It's an understanding.
레이첼은 내 전화를 안 받지
그럼 나는 왜 걸었냐고 문자를 보내고,
She ducks my call. I leave
a message with a question.
레이첼이 다시 전화하면
이번엔 내가 그 전화를 안 받고
She calls me back.
I duck that call.
그럼 문자 메시지로 용건을 말하는 거야
She leaves an answer.
그레이스 앞에서 싸울 필요가 없지
We don't have to argue
in front of Grace.
그렇게 되는군
It all works out.
그렇지
Yeah.
코노?
Kono?
다들 시작하자고
Let's go, guys.
일이 생겼어
We got something.
좋아, 호놀룰루 경찰에서
연방 보안관이랑 중대 사건 목격자 하나를
All right,
HPD assigned two officers
이송하기 위해 경관 두 명을 보냈어
to escort a federal marshal
and a high value witness
그 목격자 이름이 Julie Masters야
named Julie Masters.
그 연방 보안관은 Kahuku에 있는
The federal marshal's
been watching her
안전 가옥에서 그녀를 지키고 있었지
in a safe house in Kahuku,
이 남자가 저지른 살인 사건 재판의
and she's the key witness
in a murder trial
핵심 목격자야
against this guy,
Aaron Brenner
Aaron Brenner.
Baja 마약 카르텔의 도매상 중 하나지
He's a major distributor
for the Baja Drug Cartel.
이번 기소 건은 Julie가 없으면
제대로 되지를 않아
Now, the prosecution
cannot make a case
그리고 만약 목격자가 없다면,
without Julie,
and without a witness,
판사는 오늘 오후 5시까지
the judge is going to be forced
Brenner를 보석으로 석방해야 해
to release Brenner on bail
at 5:00 p.m. today.
좋아, 그러면 이 카르텔이 목격자를
법원에 못 가게 하기 위해서
Okay, so the cartel's going
to do everything they can
무슨 짓이든 할 거라는 얘기지?
to keep this girl out of court?
물론이지
경찰에선 이 놈을 잡아넣기 위해서
Absolutely. They've been trying
10년 동안이나 고생해 왔어
to lock this monster up
for ten years.
그리고 Julie의 증언이 있다면
너끈히 잡아넣을 수 있을 거야
And Julie's testimony can do it.
좋아, 그런데 무슨 일이 생긴 건데?
All right, where
do we come in?
호놀룰루 경찰에서 그녀를 데려오기 위해
특공대원 두 명을 보냈었는데,
HPD's lost contact
with the two SWAT guys
그 둘 모두와 통신이 끊겼대
they sent in to pick her up.
무전에 응답도 없고,
I mean, there's no comms
on the radio.
Kahuku 깊은 곳에선 휴대폰도 안 터지거든
There's no cell service
that deep in Kahuku.
그 보안관은 어떻게 됐대?
What about the marshal?
위성 휴대폰으로 걸어 봤는데
받지를 않나 봐
There's no comms
on his sat phone.
좋아, 그럼 우리가 해야 할 일이
경호야 아니면 구출이야?
Okay, so what are we,
an escort or a rescue mission?
일단은 둘 다야, 알았어?
Right now we're both. Okay?
일단 이 목격자를 찾아서 확보한 뒤에
We need to find her,
오늘 오후 5시까지
we need to secure her,
and then we need
법원으로 안전하게 데려가야 하는 거지
to transport her
to the courthouse
by 5:00 p.m. to testify.
알았어?
All right?
띵
Bing.
대니 윌리엄스 형사입니다
DANNY
This is Detective Danny Williams.
지금은 전화를 받을 수 없습니다
메시지를 남겨 주세요
I'm not available.
Please leave a message.
윌리엄스 형사, 당신 전 부인이야
Detective Williams,
this is your ex-wife.
스탠과 내가 행사에 가야 해서
I need you to pick up Grace
at 8:00 instead of 9:00
평소처럼 토요일 9시가 아니라 8시에
그레이스를 데리러 왔으면 해
on Saturday because Stan
and I are going to an event.
오, 이런!
Oh, my God!
거기 있거라, 얘야
Stay there, sweetheart.
차에서 내려!
Get out of the car.
아뇨, 제 딸을 두고는 못 가요
No, I'm not leaving my daughter.
차에서 당장 내려!
Get out of the car now.
그래요 그레이스,
시트 너머로 건너오려무나
Okay, Grace.
Get over the seat.
시트 너머로 건너와
Get over of the
seat, Grace.
빨리 건너와
Climb over the seat now.
괜찮니?
You okay?
윌리엄스 형사, 당신 전 부인이야
RACHEL Detective
Williams, this is your ex-wife.
스탠과 내가 행사에 가야 해서
I need you to pick up Grace
at 8:00 instead of 9:00
평소처럼 토요일 9시가 아니라 8시에
그레이스를 데리러 왔으면 해
on Saturday because Stan
and I are going to an event.
오, 이런!
Oh, my God!
거기 있거라, 얘야
Stay there, sweetheart.
대니?
Danny?
차에서 내려!
MAN
Get out of the car.
아뇨, 제 딸을 두고는 못 가요
No, I'm not leaving my daughter.
차에서 당장 내려!
Get out of the car now.
그레이스...
Grace, get over the seat.
Get over the seat now!
- 대니
- 그레이스는 어딨어?
Danny.
Grace. Where's Grace?
음, 일단은 괜찮아
Um, she's okay.
차량 강도를 당했어
We were carjacked.
총을 가지고 있는 놈들이었고
Um, they had guns.
지금 경찰서에 있어
We're at the police station.
거기서 나가지 마
가만히 있어
Don't move. Don't move.
5분 내로 그쪽으로 갈게
I'll be there
in five minutes.
대체 무슨 일이야?
Hey. What? What?
그레이스랑 레이첼이 차량 강도를 당했대
Grace and Rachel got carjacked.
괜찮긴 하대?
Are they okay?
나도 모르겠어
I don't know.
필요한 게 있거든 전화해
무슨 말인지 알지?
Listen, you need anything,
you call, all right?
- 뭐든 필요하면 전화해
- 알았어 가 볼게
Anything.
All right. I got to go.
얼른 가 봐
Go, go, go, go, go.
좋아, 우리도 가 보자고
All right, uh, let's go.
주위를 잘 살피게
우리가 진입한다
Secure the perimeter.
We're going in.
이봐들
Guys.
친 형, 엄호해 줘
Chin, cover me.
시체를 찾았어
I got a body.
엄호하지
I got you.
누구 시체야?
Who is it?
그 연방 보안관이야 죽었어
It's the marshal. He's gone.
코노, 진입하자고
Kono. Go.
이상 무
Clear.
좋아, 범인은 두 명이고 발이 꽤 크군
All right. We're looking
for two guys, both big.
290mm 정도 되는군
강제로 침입한 흔적은 없어
Size 11.
There's no forced entry,
그 말은 보안관이 문을 열어 뒀다는 뜻이지
which means the marshal
left the door open for them.
그들이 위협이 된다고
생각하지는 못했나봐
He didn't think
they were a threat.
경찰 제복을 입고 있었으니 그랬겠지
It's cause they
were wearing HPD uniforms.
차를 확인해 봐
Check the car.
이상 무
Clear.
부츠 발자국은
Boot prints
범인 두 놈에게서 나온 거고,
from the two assailants.
Julie Masters의 힐 자국도 있어
And Julie Masters's heels.
뭐가 있었어?
What do we got?
우리 목격자가 저항을 좀 했나 봐
Looks like our witness
was a fighter.
범인들 중 한 놈을 다치게 한 것 같아
I think she hurt one of them.
거 좋군
Good for her.
9mm 탄이야 탄피는 3개고
Nine mil. Three casings.
Julie의 지문인데
This is her print.
그러니까 범인들을 불로 공격한 다음
So she burns the shooter
창문을 깨고 거기로 나갔다 이거군
and dives through the window.
살아 있었으면 좋겠어
누군지 한번 꼭 보고 싶거든
I really hope she's alive,
'cause I want to meet her.
그래 그런데 우리 목격자가
좀 다치기도 한 거 같은데
Yeah. Looks like
she cut herself pretty good.
친 형
Chin.
그래, 스티브
Hey, Steve.
지금 경찰차 쪽에 와 있어
I'm back by the blue and whites.
봐야 할 게 좀 있는데
You need to see this.
뭐가 있었어?
What you got?
연방 보안관 한 명이랑
You kill a federal marshal
경관 두 명을 죽여 놓고서
and two officers,
the only question is
이 놈들은 대체 어디로 간 거지?
how are you going
to get put down?
그러면 지금 우리 목격자는
So she's out there
저 바깥 어디에 혼자 있는 거로군
somewhere, alone.
게다가 프로 암살자들한테 쫓기고 있겠지
And being hunted
by professional assassins.
그 놈들이 목격자를 찾기 전에
우리가 먼저 찾아내서,
So we have to find her
before they do,
오늘 증언할 수 있도록 해야 해
and make sure
she testifies today.
근데 어디서부터 시작해?
Where do we start?
좋아
All right.
물, MRE*,
* Meal, Ready-to-Eat 미군 전투식량
Water. MREs.
GPS에 위성 휴대폰
GPS. Sat phones.
알았지? 추적하는 데 필요한 것들은
이 지형들 속에 다 있어
Okay? Everything we need to
track them in this terrain.
호놀룰루 경찰도 수색견을 동원해서
추적하는 중이야
HPD is en route
with search dogs.
어이, 호놀룰루에서 공중 지원 헬기가
Hey. Just got word
that air support's lifting off
10분 뒤에 이륙한대
from Honolulu
in ten minutes.
이 근처에 헬기를 착륙시킬
They can't find a place
마땅한 곳이 없을 텐데?
to land a chopper
around here.
가장 가까운 착륙장은
여기서 48km나 떨어져 있어
Nearest LZ is
three miles away.
그래, 알았어
That's fine.
이런 빽빽한 삼림 속에서는
In this dense
foliage and canopy,
직접 들어가서 찾는 게 최선의 방책이지
our best shot at finding
her is tracking, anyway.
형, 저 장비들 좀 잘 점검해 둬
Chin, make sure these
are good to go.
그래
Copy that.
- 코노?
- 응?
Kono?
Yeah?
연방 검사랑 연락해서
Contact the U.S. Attorney, okay?
피고 Aaron Brenner에 대해서
Find out everything you can
알아낼 수 있는 건 다 알아내 봐
about this defendant
Aaron Brenner.
마약단속국 쪽도 확인해 보고
Then check with the DEA.
Baja 카르텔이 이번 일을
I want to know
who the Baja Cartel
누구에게 의뢰했는지 알아야겠어
contracts its hits through.
누구랑 상대하고 있는지는 알아야지
We need to know what we're
up against out there.
알았어 알아보도록 할게
All right. You got it.
거기들, 이리 와 봐
Guys, come on in.
이쪽 현장을 확실히 지키고 있어
We need you guys
to lock down the crime scene
목격자나 범인들이 다시 돌아올지도 모르니까
in case the witness or the
killers double back. Okay?
만약에 목격자가 돌아오면
The witness comes back,
바로 법원으로 호송하고,
you get her straight
to the courthouse.
범인들이 돌아오게 된다면
The shooters come back,
확실하게 제압해 버리고
무슨 말인지 알지?
you put them down,
and you make sure
they stay down.
그레이스?
Grace?
이리 오려무나
Come here.
이리 와
그 놈들을 봤을 때는
이미 문을 연 뒤였어요
By the time I saw him,
he'd had opened the door.
총을 가지고 있었구요
They had guns.
얘기 들었어
I heard everything.
당신 괜찮아?
Are you okay?
에드워드 부인?
Mrs. Edwards?
당신 메르세데스를 찾았습니다
We've recovered your Mercedes.
핸드백도 그대로 있고,
Your purse is intact,
현금과 신용카드도 그대로 있어요
money and credit
cards all there.
훔쳐간 건 없는 것 같습니다
Nothing seems
to be stolen.
다행이군요 고마워요
Well, that's a relief.
Thank you.
메르세데스?
스탠 차를 운전하고 있었어?
Mercedes?
You were driving Stan's car?
그래
Yeah.
태국으로 출장 갔거든
He's in Thailand
on business.
가끔 차를 바꿔 타기도 해
Sometimes we
switch cars.
잠깐 얘기 좀 하지
Let me talk to you for a second.
아빠는 저 쪽에서 엄마랑
얘기 좀 할 거야, 알았지?
I'm gonna be right there
talking to your mom, okay?
엄마랑 아빠가 보일 거야
You can see us.
이 아저씨가 뭐 하시는지 보면서
I want you to get
어떤 분인지 얘기 좀 하고 있어, 알았지?
all this guy's information,
see what he's doing, okay?
알겠습니다
All right.
이리 오려무나
Come here.
그들이 만약 그레이스를 데려갔었다면?
What if they
had taken Grace?
안 그랬잖아
그레이스를 지켰잖아 잘 했어
They didn't. You did a good job
and you protected her,
무슨 말인지 알지?
okay?
이제 어떻게 되는 거야?
What's going on?
좋아, 음...
Okay, um...
차량 강도는 징역 10년짜리 죄야
armed carjacking
is a ten-year sentence.
무슨 말인지 알겠지?
그런 위험을 무릅쓰면서까지
Okay? Rachel, anybody
willing to do that,
willing to take that risk,
차를 강도질한 다음
고작 한 시간 뒤에 버릴 리가 없어
they're not gonna just dump
the car an hour later.
만약에 누가 당신 차를 훔쳤다면,
Okay? You jack
a car for money.
10만 달러짜리 메르세데스는
Your hundred thousand
dollar Mercedes,
당장 중국 어디로 팔아 버리겠지
it gets put on a boat
to China,
2만 달러가 공짜로 생기는 거잖아
and somebody
gets a fast $20,000.
보통은 차를 버리지도 않았을 거고
핸드백도 훔쳐갔을 거고
They don't return the car,
they don't leave your purse,
현금도 그대로 두지 않았을 거야
they don't leave your cash.
그러면 대체 왜?
So why?
돈 때문에 그런 짓을 한 게
아니라는 말이야
I mean, there's
no profit motive.
대체 왜 이런 짓을 했을까?
Why would
someone do this?
아직도 모르겠어
무슨 뜻으로 말하는 거야?
Mm, I don't know.
What are you saying?
스탠이랑 같이 집에 있을 때
Anything at all strange
뭔가 이상한 점 없었어?
going on with Stan
at home? Any...
없었어
No.
확신할 수 있어?
You sure?
그래
Yes.
내가 하고 싶은 말이 뭐냐면,
누군가 메시지를 전하려고 그랬을 가능성이
Okay, 'cause I think that
there's a very high possibility
크다는 거야
that someone
is sending a message,
스탠에게 전하는 거지
'당신 부인도 우리 손에 있고,
a threat, telling Stan
that they can get to you
당신 딸도 우리 손에 있다' 라고
and they can
get to Grace.
스탠은 내 남편이고,
그레이스의 새아빠고,
Stan is my husband,
he's Grace's stepfather,
그리고... 사업가이기도 해
and... he is a
businessman.
불법적인 일하고 관련있을 리가 없어
He's not involved
in anything illegal.
그레이스를 집에 데려갔으면 해
I would like to
take Grace home.
그래, 내가 데려다 줄게
Okay, I'll drive you.
Roberts 검사입니다
Prosecuting Attorney Roberts.
칼라카와 경관, 메시지 받았습니다
뭘 도와드릴까요?
Officer Kalakaua, I got your message.
How can I help you?
오늘 있을 예정이었던 목격자 호송에 대해
아는 사람 모두의 목록이 필요합니다
I'm gonna need a list of the people who
knew about the witness transfer today.
그렇게 많지는 않아요 내 직원들이랑
마약단속국 몇몇 고위 요원들 정도죠
It's a short list-- my people
and a few high-level DEA agents.
사무실에 연락해서
I'll have my office
바로 보내드리도록 할게요
send it over to you
right away.
좋아요, 그리고 검사님 컴퓨터 시스템에
Okay, I'm also
gonna need full access
- 접속할 수 있는 권한도 필요해요
- 물론이죠
to your computer system.
Of course.
필요하신 건 모두 해 드릴게요
I'll get you
anything you need.
3명이 죽었습니다
You've got three dead.
목격자가 살아 있다고
How do you know
- 어떻게 장담하세요?
- 장담은 못 하지만 그 생지옥에서
Julie's still alive?
We don't, but she got out of the house
어떻게든 빠져나갔잖아요
그리고 바깥에 살아 있다면
against all odds,
and if she's out there,
우리가 반드시 찾아낼 겁니다
we'll find her.
이 사진들은 그 카르텔에
This is what happened
불리한 증언을 하기로 예정되어 있던
to the last three people
세 사람의 사진이예요
who were scheduled
to testify against the cartel.
어떻게 Julie Masters 같은 사람이
How does someone
like Julie Masters
Baja 카르텔과 엮인 건가요?
get involved with
the Baja Cartel?
그녀는 호놀룰루에 있는
한 무역 회사의 회계사였어요
She was an accountant at
an import company in Honolulu.
그게 Aeron Brenner의 마약 거래를 위한
She didn't know
it was a front
가짜 회사인지는 미처 몰랐겠죠
for Aaron Brenner's
drug operation.
어느 날 부두 노동자 하나가
컨테이너선 안으로 짐을 싣고 있다가
One night a dockworker
is loading crates
그들이 정말로 선적하고 있던 게
into a container ship,
discovers what they're
- 뭔지를 봐 버렸던 거죠
- 코카인이었군요
really shipping.
Cocaine.
그렇죠
Exactly.
Aaron Brenner가 그를 잡아서 죽여 버렸고,
Aaron Brenner executed
the man in cold blood,
Julie는 그 사건의 목격자예요
and Julie witnessed
the murder.
그 놈이 Julie도 죽이려고 했지만 달아났죠
He tried to kill her;
she ran.
그 때부터 지금까지
쭉 달아나는 중이죠
She's been running
ever since.
Julie가 오늘 오후 5시까지
저 법정 안에 서 있지 못하면
If Julie's not in that courtroom
by 5:00 p.m. today,
Brenner는 자유의 몸이예요
Brenner's a free man.
그 놈들이 이 길로 갔는지
어떻게 알 수 있는 거야?
How do you know
they went this way?
이런 지형에서 사람이 다닌 흔적을
추적하는 방법이 있지
Tracking humans in terrain
like this is about one thing--
자연 환경 속에 어떤 흔적이 있는지,
seeing what's
out of context in nature
그리고 왜 그런 흔적이 생겼는지를
생각해 보는 거야
and knowing what caused it.
예를 들어 보자면 저기 뒤에 있던br> 뒤집힌 바위 같은 거
Like that flat overturned rock
back up there.
저런 바위를 저렇게 만들어 놓으려면
It would've taken
a 200-pound man
몸무게가 한 90kg 정도는 되어야겠지
running downhill
to do that.
또한 하나 더,
저 바위를 보면 말이야,
That rock
also indicated
그 놈들이 대략 한 시간 전에
여기 있었다는 걸 알 수 있지
they're about an
hour ahead of us.
정말이야? 바위를 보고 그걸 알 수 있어?
Really? The rock
told you that?
형
Hey.
- 저 쪽에 나뭇잎 떨어진 거 보여?
- 응
See that leaf on the ground?
Yeah.
아직 푸른색이야
It's still green.
다시 말해 나무에서 떨어진 지
얼마 안 됐다는 말이지 엄호해 줘
It was just broken
off-- cover me.
이 쪽으로 걸어와라
Walk towards me.
경고 사격 따윈 안 한다, 알겠나?
I will not fire a warning shot.
Julie
Julie.
Julie, 무기 내려놔요, 알겠죠?
Julie, put down
the weapon, okay?
무기 얼른 내려놓고
Put down the weapon and walk
이 쪽으로 내려와요
우린 경찰입니다
towards me--
we're cops.
아까 그 두 놈도 그렇게 말했었죠
So were the last two.
약간 따끔할 겁니다
This might sting.
이제 Aaron Brenner가 도망갈 방법은 없어요
There's no way Aaron Brenner's
going to get away with this.
법원으로 데려가 주세요
You get me to that courtroom,
증언할게요
and I'll testify.
여기 이 분이 데려다 주실 겁니다
Chin will get
you there.
잠깐만, 필요할 경우를 제외하고는
Listen, don't use
절대 총을 쏘지 마, 알았지?
your gun unless
you have to, okay?
위치만 알려주는 꼴이 되고 말 거야
You don't want to draw
attention to yourself.
Julie, 신발을 제게 주세요
Julie, let me have your shoes.
벗어서 저한테 주세요
Take 'em off, give
me your shoes.
친 형,
Chin...
능선을 따라가서 Makai로 가
follow the ridgeline,
okay, head to Makai.
그렇게 되면 도로 쪽으로 갈 수 있고,
It'll lead you
back to the road
저 놈들이 형을 추적하게 된다면
and it'll give me a
better vantage point
내게 지리적 이점이 생기게 되거든
on the guys when they
pick up your trail.
알았어
Copy.
당신은 같이 안 오시나요?
Why aren't you coming with us?
당신을 해치려고 든 놈들을
I'm gonna hunt down the guys
잡으러 가야죠
that have been trying
to hurt you.
태어날 때부터 아예 간이 부은
사람들도 있는 법이랍니다
Some guys... they're just
born without a fear gene.
Aaron Brenner
Aaron Brenner.
오, 차~암 반가운 분이시군요
제 와이프라도 되십니까?
* 원문은 conjugal visit
배우자의 죄수 방문(동침 허용)을 뜻함
Oh, you must be
my conjugal visit.
당신은 호놀룰루 경찰관 두 명과
You ordered the murders
of two HPD officers
연방 보안관 한 명을 죽이도록 지시했어요
and a federal marshal.
증명할 수 있습니까?
And you can prove that?
Julie Masters는 그럴 수 있죠
Julie Masters can,
곧 여기 와서 그렇게 할 겁니다
and she'll be
here soon.
- 내 파트너들이 도와줄 테니까요
- 내 의뢰인에게서 떨어지세요
My partners will make sure of that.
Get away from my client.
목격자 분이 여기 법정에 와서 증언을 할 때
I can't wait to see the look
in your eyes when she walks
당신이 무슨 표정을 지을지 참 기대되는군요
into that courtroom
and testifies.
그거야 증언을 할 수 있긴 하다면
그렇게 되겠죠
If she testifies.
보안관 분들, 브레너 씨를 지금 당장
Sheriffs, take
Mr. Brenner
대기실로 데려가 주십시오
out of here and put him
in the holding area now.
당신을 피고를 부당하게 압박한 죄로
I'm lodging a
complaint against you
판사에게 이의제기를 하도록 하겠습니다
for harassment
with the judge.
아, 그거 좋네요 근데 어떤 분들은
제 이름 철자도 제대로 모르시던데,
You know, some people have
trouble with my name,
당신도 그러실 지 모르니
이번에 확실하게 알려드리도록 하죠
so let me help you out.
제 이름은 코노 칼라카와예요
It's Kono Kalakaua.
K-A-L-A-K-A-U-A죠
K-A-L-A-K-A-U-A.
저 문 당신이 열어둔 건 아니겠지
Don't suppose you left
that door open.
당연하지
No.
911입니다
911 operator.
무엇을 도와드릴까요?
What is your emergency?
저는 대니 윌리엄스 형사입니다
This is Detective
Danny Williams.
배지 번호는 7576이구요
My badge number is 7576.
Kuli'ou'ou의 4347 Summer 가로
경찰차 두 대를 보내 주셨으면 합니다
I need two squad cars
to 4347 Summer Street,
Kuli'ou'ou--
강도가 든 것 같습니다
possible burglary
in progress.
알겠습니다
Roger that.
지금 보내드리도록 하겠습니다
They're on their way.
고마워요
Thank you.
내 말 잘 들어
Okay, listen to me.
이 블락을 끼고 계속 돌면서 운전해
I want you to drive
around the block.
상황이 안전해지면 전화할게, 알았지?
I'll call you when
it's safe, okay?
알았어
Okay.
그레이스,
You,
엄마랑 잠깐 차에 타고 있어도 되지?
you're gonna go for a little
ride with your mom, okay?
한 5분만 어디 좀 갔다올게
I'll be out in five minutes.
"사랑해요, 대노" 이 말하는 것보다도
더 빨리 다녀올 거야, 알았지?
I'll be back faster than you can
say, "I love you, Danno," okay?
♪
차를 강도당했을 때처럼
Just like the
car, it seems
값나가는 건 하나도 안 훔쳐갔어
like nothing of
value was taken.
대신 스탠의 서재는
거의 폭풍이 휩쓸고 간 것 같더군
Stan's office looks
like a tornado hit it.
그러니 들어가서 짐을 좀 싸는 게 어때?
So why don't you go inside,
pack a bag for you and Grace?
뭐라고? 어디로 갈 건데?
What? Where...?
무슨 일이 벌어지는지
I want you to go
알아내기 전까지는
며칠 동안 호텔에 묵었으면 해
to a hotel for a couple
of days until I figure out
what is going on here.
스탠이 한 시간 뒤에 올 거야
Stan will be home
in an hour
대체 무슨 일인지 같이 알아볼 거고
and we'll figure out
what we're going to do.
스탠은 내 딸의 안전에 대해서
Okay, Stan does not
get to make decisions
결정할 권리가 없어
regarding the safety
of my daughter,
그러니까 그레이스를 데리고
힐튼 호텔에라도 가 있던가,
so she can go to
the Hilton with you
아니면 차라리 나한테 애를 맡기라고
or she can come on what
is affectionately known
as a ride along
with her father.
무슨 말인지 알았지?
Okay?
알았어 짐 쌀게
I'll pack.
하지만 그레이스가 엉망이 된 집을
보지 않았으면 해
But I don't want her
to see the house.
이미 그런 일을 겪었으니
더 겁먹기만 할 거야
It will only make her more
scared than she already is.
레이첼
Rachel.
무슨 일이 벌어지고 있는지는 모르겠지만,
Whatever is going on here,
I am telling you
그게 뭐든 간에 스탠과 관련있어
that Stan is
in the middle of it.
알았지?
Okay?
대니
Danny,
그레이스랑 레이첼은 괜찮아?
are Grace and Rachel okay?
그래, 괜찮지
하지만 나는 안 괜찮아
Yeah, they are safe,
but I am sick.
연속으로 이런 일이 터졌으니까
I'm in the middle
of a panic attack.
무슨 말인지 알지?
아주그냥 십년감수했단 말이야
Okay, this little incident
just shaved five years
off my life.
목격자는 어떻게 됐어?
What's up with the witness?
아직까지 찾고 있어?
You find her yet?
그건 걱정하지 마
Yeah, yeah,
but don't worry about that.
넌 가족들이랑 있어
Okay, you stay with your family.
- 이 쪽으로는 오지 마
- 알았어, 안 그래도 안 가고 있어
Don't come out here.
Okay, I'm not.
실은 공항으로 가는 중이야
I'm actually on my way
to the airport.
뭐? 공항에는 왜?
What are you talking about,
airport?
어디 놀러라도 가게?
Why, you going someplace?
스탠이 지금 집으로 오고 있대서
Well, Stan...
Stan comes home and, uh,
좀 같이 갈까... 하는 중이지
go offer him a lift home.
너 임마...
Hey...
대니, 지금 뭐하는 거야?
Danny, what are you doing?
아무 짓도 안 하고 있잖아
I'm not doing anything.
좀 들어 봐
Listen, okay...
네 얼굴은 안 보이지만
지금 너랑 얘기하고 있잖아
I may not be able to see you,
okay, but I can hear you,
목소리 톤은 느껴진다고
and you have a tone.
목소리 톤?
그런 거 안 넣었는데?
Tone. I don't have a tone.
- 그런 거 넣은 적 없어
- 너 그걸 꼭 이렇게 말하게 만들래?
I don't have a tone.
Okay, you say I have a face?
임마, 너 목소리 톤이 딱 있었어
You, my friend, you have a tone,
톤으로 미루어 보건대
"좀 패야 할 놈이 있어" 같은 어투였고
okay, and it's a tone that says
"I'm gonna hit somebody."
대체 뭔 일인 건데?
Now, what's going on?
알았어, 말해 주면 되잖아
Okay, I think that Stan--
내 생각에는 레이첼하고 그레이스가
그런 일들을 당한 것에
in fact I know that Stan
has something to do
스탠이 뭔가 관련이 있는 것 같아서
with what happened
to Rachel and Grace.
그래 근데 왜 그렇게 생각했는데?
Okay.
Is that based in anything
그냥 단순히 네가 스탠을 싫어해서
그렇게 생각한 것 아니야?
other than the fact
that you hate the man?
아니거든?
Yes. It is, okay?
그 놈들이 강도질한 건 스탠의 차였다고
스탠의 차 말야
They stole his car.
They-They got his car.
레이첼 차가 아니고 스탠의 차
무슨 말인지 알지?
Not hers, okay?
그리고 한 시간 뒤에 그 차가 발견됐는데,
훔쳐간 게 아무것도 없어
And they returned it in an hour,
and they didn't take anything.
그리고 집도 강도를 당해서
집안이 온통 개판이 되었는데,
All right, the house
was broken into, ransacked,
차를 강도질했을 때처럼
아무것도 훔쳐간 게 없어
and just like the car,
they took nothing.
이게 그렇게 흔한 일인 거 같아?
Okay? Does that
sound normal to you?
내 딸이 말야...
All right, my daughter...
내 딸이 그 집에서 잔다고 알지?
my daughter sleeps
in that house, okay?
그리고 스탠이 뭔가 관련이 있다면
And-and if Stan has anything
to do with it,
이 일에 대해서 아는 게 뭔지
I am going to encourage him
to tell me
싸그리 털어놓게 할 거야
what he knows.
좋아, 알았으니까 내 말 들어 봐
Okay, listen to me. All right?
너 열받은 거 알고 있어
그거 목소리 톤에서 다 티난다
I get that you're pissed,
all right? I can hear that.
하지만 뭘 하든지간에,
But whatever you do,
절대 스탠에게 손대지 마, 알았지?
do not touch him, okay?
절대 손대지 마
Do not touch him.
그래, 그건 이해하는데,
너도 내가 아버지라는 건
Yeah, I understand,
but you got to understand
마찬가지로 이해해 줘야지
that I am a father.
알아듣겠어?
그리고 이건 내 딸에 관련된 일이라고
All right?
And this is my daughter
we're talking about.
그래 그건 알겠는데,
넌 총을 가진 경찰이기도 하잖아
Yeah. You're also a cop
with a gun, okay?
그리고 그걸 잊게 되는 순간
일이 꼬이는 거야, 대니
And when those worlds cross,
it gets messy, Danny.
그래, 알았어
내가 경찰인 거 잊지 않을게
Yeah, well, I'm not the one
who crossed them.
내 걱정은 마 괜찮아
내가 알아서 할게
Just don't-don't worry about me.
Please. I will handle it.
목격자 호송이나 잘 해, 알았지?
Just get your witness
to court, okay?
아냐, 아냐 대니 대니?
No. No. Hey, hey.
Hey, hey. Danny.
대니?
Danny?
제가 첫 번째 재판이 시작됐을 때
You must think
I'm an awful person
본토로 가 버린 걸 보고
겁먹었다고 생각하셨겠죠?
for running back to the mainland
when the first trial started.
음, 당신에 대해 아는 게 없어서요
I don't know
anything about you.
왜 가셨는지는 잘 모르겠지만
I have no idea
why you left,
분명 이유가 있으셨겠죠
but I'm sure you have
your reasons.
여동생 때문이었어요
It's my sister.
저보다 다섯 살 어리죠
She's five years
younger than me.
제 가장 친한 친구예요
She's my best friend.
무슨 말인지 알겠어요
만약에 증언을 하시게 되면
All right. So you wanted
to see your sister
증인 보호 프로그램에 들어가게 되실 테니까
and you knew if
you testified,
동생 분을 보고 싶으셨던 거죠?
they'd put you in
witness protection?
무슨 말씀이신지 알겠군요
I get it.
그 사람들이 Lisa를
처음 스펙트럼 장애라고 진단했을 때,
When they first diagnosed
Lisa on the spectrum,
그게 무슨 말인지 이해하기에는
I was too young to know
저는 너무 어렸었어요
what it all meant.
동생 분이 자폐증이었나요?
She has autism?
엄마가 걔를 돌봐 주셨지만
My mom's been
taking care of her,
갈수록 그것도 힘들어졌죠
but it's getting
too hard for her.
여기서 학교를 마치고
I came here to
finish school
동생을 돌봐 주려고 온 거예요
and then I was supposed
to take care of her.
그럼 왜 갔다가 다시 오신 건가요?
Why would you come back?
Lisa가 이걸 다 이해할 것 같지가 않았죠
I didn't think Lisa
understood any of this.
어느 날 한밤중에,
그러니까 11시가 넘은 시각이었어요
And then one night, it was
late-- it was after 11:00,
보통 Lisa는 9시면 자러 가는데,
and she usually goes
to bed at 9:00--
그 날은 그 늦은 시간에 Lisa가
저를 그냥 쳐다보고 있더라고요
she just looked at me,
그리고는 하는 말이,
제가 하와이로 돌아가서
and she said that I had
to go back to Hawaii
그 나쁜 놈들이 더 이상 그 누구도
해치지 못하도록 해야 한다고 말하더라고요
and make sure that the bad man
didn't hurt anyone else.
오
Oh.
용감하시군요
You're a brave woman.
세 명이 더 죽었고,
Three more people are dead,
동생을 다시 못 볼지도 모르지만요,
and I may never see my sister.
꼭 법정에 가서 증언을 할 거예요
I have to get back
to that courthouse.
그래요 어서 가요
All right, let's go.
좋아요
Okay.
이제 반 좀 넘게 왔군요
We're more than halfway now.
잘 하고 계세요
You're doing great.
엎드려요!
Get down!
꼭 잡아요
Hold on.
손 꼭 잡아요
Hold on. Okay.
셋 세면 끌어올릴게요
I'm going to pull you up
on three.
아시겠죠?
Okay?
하나, 둘,
One, two,
셋
three.
길을 따라서 쭉 가세요
Keep going straight ahead.
바로 뒤에서 따라갈게요
I'll be right behind you.
괜찮아요 접니다
It's okay.
It's okay. It's me.
방금 그 놈을 속여서
다른 방향으로 가게 했어요
Now, I've pointed him
in another direction,
하지만 곧 눈치채고 따라올 겁니다
but he's going
to figure it out soon enough.
그러니 계속 움직여야 해요 아시겠죠?
We've just got
to keep moving, okay?
쭉 가는 겁니다 출발하죠
Straight ahead.
Let's go.
일어나셨구만
You're up.
좋아
Good.
질문 몇 개 좀 하자
I wanted to ask you
a couple questions.
네 놈 일당들이
하와이에 얼마나 온 거지?
How many of you
were sent to Hawaii?
대답 안 할 거야?
내가 두 번 묻게 할 텐가?
Seriously? You going to make me
ask you twice right now?
세 명이야 세 명이서 왔어
Three of us were sent here.
어디서 왔나?
Where did you fly in from?
San Jose
San Jose.
코스타리카
Costa Rica.
이걸 만드는 게
얼마나 쉬운 일이었는지 봤지?
See how easy that was?
부탁이야
Please.
원하는 건 다 이야기해 줬잖아
I told you
what you want to know.
네 놈을 고문하지는 않을 거야
I'm not going
to torture you, okay?
네 목숨을 구해 주려고 하는 중이지
I'm going to save your life.
폐가 무기폐*더군
* 원문은 collapsed lung
폐의 일부가 팽창된 상태를 유지하지 못하고,
부피가 줄어 쭈그러든 상태를 뜻한다
이 증상을 보이는 병으로 기흉 등이 있음
You have a collapsed lung.
가슴에 구멍을 뚫어서
I need to cut a
hole in your chest
폐를 다시 팽창시키지 않으면
and reinflate your lung,
넌 죽어 무슨 말인지 알겠어?
or you're going to die.
All right?
이걸 물고 있는 게 좋을 거야
You may want to chew on that.
꽉 물고, 소리는 내지 말고
Don't make any noise.
코노입니다
Kono.
친 형한테서 소식 들은 거 있어?
Did you hear from Chin Ho?
없어
No.
무슨 일이야?
같이 있던 거 아니었어?
Why? You don't have eyes on him?
아냐, 흩어졌어
하지만 형이 목격자를 데리고 있지
No. We split up,
but he has the witness.
걱정 마, 괜찮을 거야
뭐 알아낸 거 있어?
Don't worry, he'll be fine.
What do you got?
습격자들의 신원은
I still have no ID
아직 파악하지 못했어
그쪽은 좀 어때?
on the hit squad.
Any luck on your end?
놈들 중 한 명을 잡았어
Yeah. I disabled
one of the attackers.
자기가 어제 코스타리카에서 날아온
He confessed to
being part of the team
팀원들 중 한 명이라고 자백하더군
that flew in from
Costa Rica yesterday.
알았어 어제 온 코스타리카발 항공편의
탑승 명단을 조회해 볼게
Okay. I'm checking flight
manifests from Costa Rica.
이 놈 말로는
암살자들은 세 명이라는군
He said there were
three assassins, okay?
그건 다른 말로 하면
4명을 찾아야 한다는 뜻이지
Which means we're looking
for four people--
세 명은 나서서 총질하는 놈들이고
한 명은 'Cleaner' 야
three shooters and a cleaner.
Cleaner? 그게 뭔데?
Cleaner? What's a cleaner?
나머지 셋과 마찬가지로 암살자야
SEAL*에서 근무하던 시절에
* US Navy SEALs 미 해군 특수부대
맥개럿이 이 부대 소령이다
It's another assassin.
My SEAL team used
이런 놈들을 상대해 본 적이 있거든
나머지 세 명은 Cleaner가 누군지 몰라
to hunt squads like this.
The shooters don't know
the identity of the cleaner,
그러니까 그 놈들이 잡혀도
나머지 한 놈이 여전히 남아서
so if they get captured,
there's still another shooter
원래 계획대로 암살을 하는 거지
in place to pull the trigger.
좋아 어제 코스타리카에서 출발한
호놀룰루행 항공편은
All right.
There was one flight in
딱 하나야
from Costa Rica
to Honolulu yesterday.
그리고...
And...
탑승객들 중 세 명이
티켓 값을 현금으로 냈어
three of the passengers
paid in cash.
좋아, 그 세 놈 혹시
Okay, can you pull them up
보안 카메라에 잡힌 영상 있어?
on the security cam?
찾았어
I got them.
음, 그런데 문제가...
You know what?
Cleaner라고 하는 네 번째 놈이 안 보여
I'm not seeing the fourth guy
who could be the cleaner.
얼굴 인식 시스템에 돌려 봐
Run facial recognition.
전과자 데이터베이스 쪽에다가
Go through the records.
Cleaner가 누군지 알아낼 만한
Look for any clues
that might lead
단서를 찾아보는 거야
to the cleaner.
아참, 응급구조대에 연락해서
환자 후송 헬기를 좀 보내 줘
In the meantime,
have EMS send a medevac.
일단 숲에 들어온 다음
지금 불러주는 좌표로 걸어서 오라고 해
Tell them to insert
and then proceed on foot
2797에...
to coordinates 27.97
15695로
-156.95.
그렇게 할게
Will do.
좋아
All right.
- 저 쪽입니다
Hilton Hawaiian Viliage 713호죠
- 고맙습니다
Hey, there. Hilton Hawaiian
Village, room 713. Thanks.
당신과 그레이스가 무사해서 다행이야
Just thank God you and Grace
are okay, baby.
그래
Yeah.
지금 가는 중이야
All right, listen.
I'm on the way.
곧 도착할 거야
I'll be there soon.
이봐
Hey.
대니?
Danny?
그래 얘기 좀 하자
Yeah. I got to talk to you.
지금 부탁하는 거 아니야
이리 와
I'm not asking you.
Come on.
빨랑 오라고
자네도 알다시피 스탠,
You know, Stan,
내 딸을 내가 키웠을 때는
when I had a daughter,
내가 앞으로 맞닥드려야 할
몇 가지 것들이
I knew that there
were certain things
있다는 걸 확실히 알고 있었지
I was going to
have to deal with.
딸래미가 문자질하는 거 하며,
옷 사는 데 드는 엄청난 돈,
Texting.
An obscene clothing budget.
뒷골 당기게 하는
A stroke-inducing
문자 메시지 요금까지 있었지만
전부 개의치 않았었어
cell phone bill, regardless
of the plan that I chose,
하지만 하나 말해 두겠는데,
but I'll tell you,
그런 것들 목록에
절대 안 들어갔던 게 있어
there is one thing that
did not make the list. Okay.
차량 강도
Carjacking.
차량 강도는...
Carjacking did
not make the list
내 여덟살짜리 딸과 함께
맞닥뜨릴 일이라고는
of things that I thought
that I would encounter
상상조차 못 했었다고
with my eight-year-old daughter.
그러니 딱 한 번만 질문하지
So I am going
to ask you one time.
너 대체 무슨 일이 있는 거야?
What kind of trouble
are you in?
나랑은 아무 상관 없는 일이야, 대니
This has nothing
to do with me, Danny.
네가 충격받은 만큼 나도 충격받았다고
I'm as shocked as you are.
닥쳐
Shut up.
입 다물고 있어 알았어?
Shut up. Okay?
하나 알았으면 하는 게 있는데,
I want you to know something.
원래 내 성깔대로 했으면
네 놈을 때려 눕힌 다음
Normally, I would just pull over
and give you the worst beating
진실을 말할 때까지
흠씬 두들겨패 줬겠지만
you ever had in your entire life
until you told me the truth,
공교롭게도 나는 말이지,
but I am working,
I am working
지금 분노를 조절하는 중이고,
이런 일을 좋게 해결하려고
on my anger management issues,
and I am learning
애쓰는 중이야 알아듣겠어?
conflict resolution,
you understand?
그리고 나는 이미 눈치를 챘으니까
And I recognize something.
I recognize,
네가 아무리 숨겨 봤자 소용없어
although you are trying
to hide it,
겁먹은 거 알고 있어
물론 마땅히 그래야 하고
you are very scared right
now, as you should be,
하지만 너한테 기회를 주지
but I am going to give you
무죄추정의 원칙이란 게 있는 거니까
사실대로 털어놔 그리고 이걸 잊지 마라
the benefit of the doubt
and I am going to remind you
너 때문에 내 딸한테
총을 들이댄 놈들이
that because of you,
people put guns
있었다는 것을
near my daughter.
공공주택 담당관을 좀 만났었어
I went
to the housing commissioner,
이름이 Bruce Hoffman이야
Bruce Hoffman,
새로 산 부동산에 대한
허가를 받으러 갔었는데,
for permits
for my new property.
뉴욕의 Cipriani* 식당에서나 볼 법한
메뉴판을 내놓더라고
* 뉴욕에 위치한 고급 식당
단, Cipriani는 회사 이름이다 본사는 룩셈부르크
Guy hands me a menu like we're
at Cipriani's in New York.
전부 가격이 매겨져 있었지
뇌물을 달라는 소리였어
Everything's got a price.
그래서 돈을 주겠다고 하면
Every time I agreed to a number,
더 달라고 요구했었어
he jacked it up
to a higher one.
그래서 대화를 녹음해서는
So I taped the conversation,
고발하겠다고 놈에게 말했었지
told him I'd
have him indicted.
이제 알겠구만
놈들은 그 테이프를 찾던 거였군
So that's what
they're looking for. The tapes?
대니, 신께 맹세하는데, 난 절대...
Danny, I swear to God,
I never...
그냥 나한테 먼저 얘기할 수는 없었어?
Why didn't you just come to me?
자네 지금 농담해?
Are you kidding?
절대 아니지
No, I'm not.
이봐,
Look,
최근에 레이첼이랑 나랑
things haven't been great
잘 되지 못한 일들이 많았지만
with Rachel and me lately.
여전히 레이첼을 사랑해
그리고 그레이스도 사랑하고
But I love her, Danny,
and I love Grace.
이렇게라도 해야
일을 더 잘 풀어나갈 수 있을 거야
This deal could make a lot
of things right for us.
그래, 일단 들어 봐
Okay. Uh, listen.
레이첼이랑 그레이스는
힐튼 호텔에 묵을 거야
Grace and Rachel are going
to be staying at the Hilton...
너 정말로 그렇게 생각...
You really think...
놈들이 네 차를 강도질했다고
Hey. They jacked your car.
집에도 침입해 들어갔고
They broke into
your house.
그리고 그레이스는 내 딸이야
그러니 그렇게 생각하고말고
That is my daughter.
So, yes, Stan, I think.
여기 있어요 잔돈은 가지세요
Here you go. Keep the rest.
공공 주택 담당관님 되십니까?
Aren't you the
housing commissioner?
Bruce Hoffman입니다
Bruce Hoffman.
이봐요
Hey.
이 방을 좀 비워 주셔야겠습니다
I need this room.
Come on.
빨리빨리들 나가 주세요
Come on, come on.
자, 빨리빨리요 나가 주세요
Go ahead. Come
on, out, out.
난 대니 윌리엄스 형사라고 합니다
I'm Detective Danny Williams.
그리고 댁이 오늘 아침에
습격하라고 시켰던
I am also the father
of that little girl
메르세데스에 타고 있던
어린아이의 아버지이기도 하고
that was in the
Mercedes that you had
carjacked this morning,
아마 스탠 에드워드에게
메시지를 보내려고 한 짓이겠지
sending a message
to Stan Edwards.
테이프는 내가 가지고 있수다
스탠에겐 없소
I have the tapes now.
He doesn't have them anymore.
그러니 뭐 하나 물읍시다
I'm going to ask
you a question.
그 테이프들이 공개된다면
What do you think would happen
무슨 일이 벌어질 것 같으쇼?
if those tapes got out?
대답해 보슈
Huh?
이봐요, 잠시만요
지금 당신이 무슨 말을 하는지
Look, look.
I... I don't know anything
하나도 못 알아듣겠어요
about what
you're talking about,
형사님 성함이...
Detective...
윌리엄스다
Williams.
윌리엄스
네 놈 코앞에 배지를 들이댔으니
이제 확실히 알겠지
You can get my badge number
off your forehead.
내가 그 테이프를 가지고 있어
그리고 경고하지
I have those tapes,
and will expose you,
만약에 네 놈이 앞으로
and if you ever, ever
한 번만 더 내 딸이 사는 집에
총을 들이댔다간,
put a gun in the same
zip code as my daughter,
신께 맹세코 네 놈을 죽여 버리겠어
I swear to God,
I will kill you.
알아듣겠나?
You understand?
- 네
- 알아듣겠어?
Yeah.
Yeah?
- 네
- 좋아
Yes.
Good.
제 옆에 있으세요
Stay close.
Okay.
들어오세요
제기랄......
Damn it.
잠시만요
Hold on.
그냥 헬기를 부르면 안 되나요?
Can't you just call
for a helicopter?
제 핸드폰이 총이랑 같이
절벽 밑으로 떨어져 버렸어요
My phone
went down the cliff
with my gun.
한 시간밖에 안 남았어요
We've only got an hour left.
이걸 타고 갈 수 있을 겁니다
This bike'll get us there.
저 자도 놈들 중 한 명이었나요?
Is he one of them?
아뇨
No.
자세 낮추고 있으세요
Stay down.
친, 그 자예요
Chin, it's him.
그 때 그 놈들 중 하나예요
It's the other guy.
이 쪽으로 오고 있어요
He's coming around.
움직이지 마세요
Hold on.
바이크에 얼른 타요!
Get on the bike!
얼른 타
Get in.
여기는 스티브 맥개럿 소령이다
This is Lieutenant Commander
Steve McGarrett.
목격자 Julie Masters를 확보했으며
The witness, Julie Masters,
is secure,
그녀를 데려가는 중이다
and we're bringing her in.
법원 주위에 무장 병력을
All right,
I want an armed perimeter
배치해 주기 바란다
guarding the courthouse.
아직 누구인지 알아내지 못한
There's still
a potential assassin
암살자가 있을 수 있다
who has not
been apprehended.
트럭을 타고 가는 중이다
We're coming in
by truck.
보면 무슨 트럭인지 알 수 있을 것이다
You'll know which truck,
trust me.
음, 제 차에 여분의 신발 한 켤레랑
스웨터가 있어요
Uh, I have an extra pair of
shoes and a sweater in my car.
어서 가죠
We got to go.
고마워요
Thank you.
정말 너무너무 감사해요
For everything.
더 이상 도망칠 일은 없을 겁니다
No more running.
가세요
Go.
드디어 목격자 분을 데려오셨군요
I see that you've finally
produced your witness.
네, 증언할 준비도 되셨답니다
She's ready to testify.
제 의뢰인이 사법 거래를 제안하더군요
My client would like
to talk about a deal.
유죄를 인정하고
He pleads guilty
and gives up the names
경찰 두 명과 연방 보안관을 살해한
of his suppliers
and his coconspirators
공범들과 공급책들의 이름을 넘겨주는 대신에
in the murders of the two cops
and the federal marshal
사형 없는 종신형을 원한다는군요
in exchange for life in prison
with no death penalty.
그렇게 하면 그는 사형 대신에
평생을 감방에서 썩는 거고,
He dies in prison instead
of being executed,
그 대가로 우리는
and in exchange,
Aaron Brenner 같은 놈들 열 명 정도는
더 감방에 잡아넣을 수 있을 거예요
we get to put ten more Aaron
Brenners away for life, Julie.
공동 변호인은 어디 있나요?
그 사람도 사인을 해야 할 텐데요
Where's your co-counsel?
He has to sign off on this.
회의실에서 기다리고 계세요
He's waiting
in the conference room.
그래, 코노
Hey, Kono.
그 Cleaner가 누군지 알아냈어요
Brenner의 공동 변호인이예요
Hey, the cleaner
is Brenner's co-counsel.
키 170cm 정도에 금발머리 여자예요
She's a blonde woman,
five, seven,
그리고 지금 그 법원 안에 있고요
and she's in the courthouse
right now.
그는 어디 있습니까?
Where is he?
곧 올 겁니다
He'll be right in.
너한테 가르칠 만한 것들이
몇 가지 있긴 하지만
You know, there might be a few
other things I could teach you,
이런 놈들 때려잡는 기술 하나는
확실히 배워둔 것 같으니 필요 없겠네
but I think you've got the whole
ass-kicking thing down.
모든 게 괜찮은 거야?
Is everything all right?
그래, 지금은 괜찮아
대니 덕분이지
Yeah, it is now,
thanks to Danny.
그래, 오해가 좀 있었을 뿐이야
Yeah, it was just a...
misunderstanding.
스탠은 그냥...
You know,
그 일에 휘말린 것뿐이었으니까
Stan just got caught
in the middle of it.
그게 잘못은 아니잖아
You know,
it wasn't his fault.
이젠 다 끝났어
It's over now.
- 다시 한 번 고마워, 대니
- 그래
Thanks again, Danny.
All right.
그레이스
You.
나중에 또 보자, 알았지?
I'll see you later, okay?
그래요 사랑해요, 대노
Okay. I love you, Danno.
나도 사랑한단다
I love you, too.
이리 오려무나, 얘야
Come on, kiddo.
다시 한 번 고맙네
Thanks again.
재판장님, 원고 측은 증인으로
Your Honor, the prosecution
Julie Masters 씨를 신청합니다
calls Julie Masters.
이 법정에서 알고 있는 모든 진실을 말할 것을,
Do you swear
to tell the truth,
그리고 오직 진실만을 말할 것을 맹세합니까?
the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth?
맹세합니다
I do.
보아주셔서 감사합니다
피드백은 usnseals@naver.com으로 보내주세요
Sync, corrected by elderman
for www.addic7ed.com